# Persian Named Entity Recognition Dataset
# Format: TOKEN TAG
# Tags: B-PER (Beginning Person), I-PER (Inside Person), B-LOC (Beginning Location), I-LOC (Inside Location), B-ORG (Beginning Organization), I-ORG (Inside Organization), O (Other)

علی B-PER
احمدی I-PER
در O
تهران B-LOC
زندگی O
می‌کند O
. O

شرکت B-ORG
ایران I-ORG
خودرو I-ORG
در O
سال O
۱۳۹۵ O
تأسیس O
شد O
. O

دکتر B-PER
محمد I-PER
رضا I-PER
کریمی I-PER
در O
دانشگاه B-ORG
تهران I-ORG
تدریس O
می‌کند O
. O

شهر B-LOC
اصفهان I-LOC
یکی O
از O
زیباترین O
شهرهای O
ایران B-LOC
است O
. O

بانک B-ORG
ملی I-ORG
ایران I-ORG
یکی O
از O
بزرگترین O
بانک‌های O
کشور O
است O
. O

استاد B-PER
احمد I-PER
محمدی I-PER
در O
دانشگاه B-ORG
شریف I-ORG
پژوهش O
می‌کند O
. O

شهر B-LOC
مشهد I-LOC
مقدس I-LOC
در O
شمال O
شرق O
ایران B-LOC
قرار O
دارد O
. O

شرکت B-ORG
سایپا I-ORG
یکی O
از O
بزرگترین O
خودروسازان O
ایران B-LOC
است O
. O

دکتر B-PER
فاطمه I-PER
احمدی I-PER
متخصص O
قلب O
و O
عروق O
است O
. O

شهر B-LOC
شیراز I-LOC
پایتخت O
فرهنگی O
ایران B-LOC
محسوب O
می‌شود O
. O
